I was always so sickly and so weak you
know get dizzy spells and you know feel
like fainting and Sapphira
nick open up Akita Simon a cow then I
constantly couldn't say yes to work
because that's always feeling not okay I
waited to go see my doctor and he had
told me that they had found a lump in my
breast and I said but that's normal some
women really do have lumps in their
breast or it could be a hormonal thing
but then he said it was alarming because
they had also found a lump in my lymph
node at that very moment I wasn't afraid
about dying or having cancer or or being
sick I immediately brought my attention
to my son and his future and what am i
leaving behind for him the moment I got
back I was really scrounging around
trying to prepare for whatever I can
like if if I do have cancer at least I'm
prepared and can do whatever I can and
if I don't then that's great too and I
still have to prepare to be honest you
know until up until this happens to me I
just found insurance so complicated but
sometimes you know God will knock you in
the head just to show you hey this is
what you're supposed to be doing this is
what you need at the moment I think this
was definitely a wake-up call for me it
made me think about that that I'm not
indestructible that I'm not gonna live
forever and that I might not always be
there for my son
they taught me to put my son first
in order to put my son first up it means
that I would have to take care of myself
also what I love about seven for health
is they cover you up the three critical
illnesses they cover you comprehensively
all the way up till you're 75 and if you
don't get sick you get all your money
back
it's money small percentages that you're
putting away that that will come in
handy when you need it or that you can
take with you even when you don't when
you're older
I can constantly feel like I'm preparing
for what's about to happen whenever it
happens